Lilly Andrews

4S6 Your Street, Victoria, TX 12345 youremai l@ e maiLexa mple.com (123) 456-7890

Skilled, professional babysitter with a flexible schedule and over 7 years of experience providing exceptional, loving care to infants, toddlers and children of all ages. Knowledgeable in child development stages, communication best practices and positive behavior reinforcement. Certified in CPR and first aid.

Education

Master of Science in Early Childhood Education

Texas A&M University, College Station, TX September 2012 - July 2014

Bachelor of Science

Texas A&M University, College Station,TX September 2008 - May 2012

Key Skills

- Compassionate
- Creative
- · Excellent communication skills
- · Highly organized
- Knowledge of early childhood development and age-appropriate activities
- Years of experience providing exceptional childcare

Certifications

- Completion of the American Heart Association's Heartsaver Pediatric First Aid CPR AED Course
- Child and Baby First Aid/CPR/AED Certification, American Red Cross

Professional Experience

Babysitter

Richardson Family, Victoria, TX 1 February 2016 - Present

- Provide ongoing part-time childcare to three children between the ages of 14 months and 8 years
- Manage and supervise children's after-school activities
- Maintain a safe, clean and organized environment within the household
- Drive and escort children to scheduled appointments and on fun outings to Local parks and children's museums

Nanny

Martinez Family, San Antonio, TX I November 2010- February 2016

- Served as child's full-time nanny while the parents were working
- Prepared all snacks and meals for child in the parents' absence
- Facilitated learning opportunities and age-appropriate activities for the child
- Took the child on nature walks in nearby parks
- Provided parents with regular updates on the child's development and notable events